Guide to the Agenda Records
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Writings, 1925-1984; Series I; 15.5; (31 boxes)
  - Mu, Yin
    - "On The Lyons Bus," typescript, original and translated by John Cayley, undated (Box 21, Folder 1435)
  - Muir, Edwin
    - "Our Contemporary and Mentor," galley, with author's corrections, undated (Box 21, Folder 1436)
  - Muller, Chris
    - [Review] "Miroslav Holub: On the Contrary and other poems," typescript corrected, 1984 Dec 11 (Box 21, Folder 1437)
  - Mulrine, Stephen
    - "The Coming of the Wee Malkies," typescript, corrected, 1967 Mar (Box 21, Folder 1438)
  - Muses, C.A.
    - "Thoughts on Today," typescript, corrected, undated (Box 21, Folder 1439)
  - Naum, Gellu
    - "The Persistancy of Flames," translated by Dan Dutescu, typescript, corrected, undated (Box 21, Folder 1440)
  - Neame, Alan
    - "Epigram on a Hungarian Refugee," typescript, corrected, undated (Box 21, Folder 1441)
    - "London Transport," typescript, corrected, undated (Box 21, Folder 1442)
    - "The Monument," typescript, undated (Box 21, Folder 1443)
    - ["Office Hymn,"] typescript, corrected, undated (Box 21, Folder 1444)
    - "Snails in March-Lebanon"
      - Typescript, undated (Box 21, Folder 1445)
      - Typescript, corrected, 1957 Mar 12 (Box 21, Folder 1446)
    - Empty folder (Box 21, Folder 1447)
    - "Typing Under The Bed"
      - Typescript, corrected, undated (Box 21, Folder 1448)
      - Galley, undated (Box 21, Folder 1449)
  - Nemoianu, Virgil
    - "Contemporary Romainian Poetry," typescript, corrected, undated (Box 21, Folder 1450)
  - Nerval, Gérard de
    - "Christ in the Olive Grove," translated by Peter Thompson
      - Typescript, undated (Box 21, Folder 1451)
      - Galley, with translator's corrections, undated (Box 21, Folder 1452)
  - Niedecker, Lorine
    - "The Ballad of Basil," printed version, 1976 (Box 21, Folder 1453)
  - Noble, R.W.
    - [Review] "Flight Beyond The Iron Gate"
      - Typescript, corrected, undated (Box 21, Folder 1454)
      - Galley, with author's corrections, undated (Box 21, Folder 1455)
  - Nordberg, Donald
    - "At the Reflecting Pool," typescript, undated (Box 21, Folder 1456)
  - O'Driscoll, Dennis
    - [Review] " British Poetry Since 1970: A Critical Survey edited by Peter Jones and Michael Schmidt," typescript, corrected, undated (Box 21, Folder 1457)
    - "Elegies," typescript, undated (Box 21, Folder 1458)
    - [Review] The Flood by Charles Tomlinson, typescript, corrected, undated (Box 21, Folder 1459)
    - [Review] A Night In The Gazebo, by Alan Brownjohn, typescript, corrected, undated (Box 21, Folder 1460)
    - [Review] The Oxford Book Of Contemporary Verse 1945-1980 chosen by D.J. Enright"
      - Typescript, corrected, undated (Box 21, Folder 1461)
      - Galley, corrected, undated (Box 21, Folder 1462)
    - [Review] " Sea To The West by Norman Nicholson," typescript, corrected, undated (Box 21, Folder 1463)
    - [Review] " Songs A Thracian Taught Me ," by Anne Beresford, typescript, corrected, undated (Box 21, Folder 1464)
    - [Reviews] " Unhistorical Fragments ," by John Whitworth [and] " Victorian Voices ," by Anthony Thwaite, typescript, corrected, undated (Box 21, Folder 1465)
  - O'Grady, Desmond
    - "Ezra Pound: A Personal Memoir"
      - Typescript, corrected and holograph, 1979 Nov (Box 21, Folder 1466)
      - Typescript, corrected, undated (Box 21, Folder 1467)
      - Galley, corrected, undated (Box 21, Folder 1468)
    - "Versions From Greek"
      - Typescript, corrected, undated (Box 21, Folder 1469)
      - Galleys, corrected, undated (Box 21, Folder 1470)
        With: APcS from Desmond O'Grady to William Cookson, 1980 Jan 14
      - Galley, corrected, undated (Box 21, Folder 1471)
  - O'Higgins, M.C.
    - [Quotation from,] typescript, undated (Box 22, Folder 1472)
  - Oliver, Michael
    - "Kaleiderscope," typescript, 1981 Jul 21 (Box 22, Folder 1473)
  - Oppen, George
    - "The Young Age: The Road on the Coast," typescript, undated (Box 22, Folder 1474)
  - Orlen, Steve
    - "Four Poems"
      - Typescript, undated (Box 22, Folder 1475)
      - Galley, with author's corrections, undated (Box 22, Folder 1476)
      - Galley, corrected, undated (Box 22, Folder 1477)
  - Orr, Peter
    - "Mr Jones Your Legs are Crossed"
      - Typescript, undated (Box 22, Folder 1478)
        With: TLS from Peter Orr to William Cookson, 1977 May 23
      - Typescript, corrected, undated (Box 22, Folder 1479)
      - Galley, with author's corrections, undated (Box 22, Folder 1480)
        With: ALS to William Cookson from Peter Orr, 1977 Jul 29
      - Galley, corrected, undated (Box 22, Folder 1481)
  - Ou-yang, Hsiu (Ouyang, Xiu)
    - "Lyric," translated by John Cayley, poem, typescript, original and corrected, undated (Box 22, Folder 1482)
  - Ovid
    - "Eight Translations from Ovid's Metamorphoses ," translated by A. D. Melville, typescript, corrected, undated (Box 22, Folder 1483)
  - Ozturk, Tony
    - [Review] "Poet Among Painter," typescript, corrected, undated (Box 22, Folder 1484)
    - "Two Poems," typescript, undated (Box 22, Folder 1485)
  - Palmer, Penelope
    - [Review] "C.H. Sisson"
      - Typescript, corrected, undated (Box 22, Folder 1486)
      - Galley, with author's corrections, 1977 (Box 22, Folder 1487)
        With: ANS to William Cookson from Penelope Palmer, 1977 Jul 20
      - Galley, corrected, undated (Box 22, Folder 1488)
    - "The Chandelier," typescript, corrected, undated (Box 22, Folder 1489)
    - [Review] "Charles Tomlinson: 'The Way In' and other poems," typescript, ca.1974 Oct 31 (Box 22, Folder 1490)
    - "The Cornflowers"
      - Typescript, corrected, undated (Box 22, Folder 1491)
      - Galley, with author's corrections, undated (Box 22, Folder 1492)
    - "Death of an Englishman's Friend," typescript, undated (Box 22, Folder 1493)
    - The Lamp [Agenda Editions], notice, 3c. (Box 22, Folder 1494)
    - [Review] "Osip Mendelstam: Poems chosen and translated by James Green"
      - Typescript, corrected, undated (Box 22, Folder 1495)
      - Galley, with author's corrections, undated (Box 22, Folder 1496)
      - Galley, corrected, undated (Box 22, Folder 1497)
    - [Review] "Randall Jarrell: The Third Book of Criticism ," typescript, corrected, 1975 Jan 20 (Box 22, Folder 1498)
    - "Water"
      - Typescript, undated (Box 22, Folder 1499)
      - Galley, undated (Box 22, Folder 1500)
    - "Zadarpopski," typescript, undated (Box 22, Folder 1501)
  - Pao, Chao (Bao Zhao)
    - "Sitting Up at Night," translated by John Cayley, typescript, undated (Box 22, Folder 1502)
  - Paris, John
    - "Pauline," typescript, undated (Box 22, Folder 1503)
  - Patchett, John
    - "Cards," typescript, undated (Box 22, Folder 1504)
    - "Cinquefoil," typescript, undated (Box 22, Folder 1505)
    - "Deep Gill for R. W."
      - Typescript, undated (Box 22, Folder 1506)
      - Galley, with author's corrections, undated (Box 22, Folder 1507)
    - "Grandmother," typescript, undated (Box 22, Folder 1508)
    - "Kate," typescript, undated (Box 22, Folder 1509)
    - "Pavanne 1" and "Pavanne 2 [sic.]," typescript, undated (Box 22, Folder 1510)
    - [Response to the rhythm questionnaire,] galley, with author's corrections, undated (Box 22, Folder 1511)
    - "Le Sang des Autres," typescript, undated (Box 22, Folder 1512)
    - "Theseus," typescript, undated (Box 22, Folder 1513)
  - Paunescu, Adrian
    - "Quill," typescript, corrected, undated (Box 22, Folder 1513a)
  - Pavlopoulos, George
    - "The Cellar," translated, and with an introduction by Peter Levi, typescript, 1974 (Box 22, Folder 1514)
  - Pearlman, Daniel D.
    - "The Blue - Eyed Eel. Dame Fortune in Pound's Later Cantos," typescript, undated (Box 22, Folder 1515)
    - "The Inner Metronome: a Genetic Study of Time in Pound," typescript, corrected, undated (Box 22, Folder 1516)
    - "A Political Satire Unveiled: Frost's Neither Out Far Nor in Deep
      - Typescript, corrected, with abstract, undated (Box 22, Folder 1517)
      - Galley, with author's corrections, undated (Box 22, Folder 1518)
  - Peck, John
    - "Canzone," typescript, undated (Box 23, Folder 1519)
    - "Cussewago," printed version, undated (Box 23, Folder 1520)
      With" TLS to William Cookson from John Peck, 1973 Jun 2
    - "Geoffrey Hill's Tenebrae
      - Typescript, corrected, undated (Box 23, Folder 1521)
      - Galley, corrected, undated (Box 23, Folder 1522)
      - Galley, undated (Box 23, Folder 1523)
    - "Hardy and the Figure in Scene"
      - Typescript, corrected, undated (Box 23, Folder 1524)
      - Galley, with author's corrections, undated
    - "Landscape as Ceremony in the Later Cantos: From 'The Roads of France' to Rock, undated (Box 23, Folder 1525)
    - "Little Frieze"
      - Typescript, undated (Box 23, Folder 1526)
      - Galleys, with author's corrections, undated (Box 23, Folder 1527)
    - "Pound and Hardy"
      - Typescript, corrected, undated (Box 23, Folder 1528)
      - Galley, with author's corrections, undated (Box 23, Folder 1529)
    - "Route Toward the World in Common," typescript, undated (Box 23, Folder 1530)
    - "Two Poems"
      - Typescript, undated (Box 23, Folder 1531)
      - Galley, corrected, undated (Box 23, Folder 1532)
    - [Two Poems,] galley, corrected, undated (Box 23, Folder 1533)
  - Peck, John, (translator)
    - "A Christian Epigram from the Palatine Anthology (L. 59)"
      - Typescript, undated (Box 23, Folder 1534)
      - Galley, undated (Box 23, Folder 1535)
  - Peng, Yen-chio (Peng Yanjiao)
    - "The Young Calf," unidentified translator, printed version, undated (Box 23, Folder 1536)
  - Perloff, Marjorie
    - "Fearlessly Holding Back Nothing: Robert Lowell's Last Poems:" typescript, undated (Box 23, Folder 1537)
  - Petty, W. H.
    - "Two Poems"
      - Typescript, undated (Box 23, Folder 1538)
      - Galley, undated (Box 23, Folder 1539)
        With: ALS to William Cookson from W. H. Petty, 1981 Oct 27
  - Pavese, Cesare
    - "You are earth and death," translated by Mariolina Freeth, typescript, corrected, 1962 (Box 23, Folder 1540)
  - Philippide, Alexandru
    - "The Incommunicable," typescript, undated (Box 23, Folder 1541)
  - Phillips, Roy
    - "Words and Butterflies," galleys, undated (Box 23, Folder 1542)
  - Pien, Chih-lin (Bian Zhilin)
    - "The Development of China's 'New Poetry' and the Influence From the West," typescript, 4th revision, 1979-81 (Box 23, Folder 1543)
    - "Dream of an Old Town," unidentified translator, printed version, undated (Box 23, Folder 1544)
    - "Evacuated Peasants," translated by Hu Shiguang, and "A Long Journey," translated by Eugene Eoyang, printed version, undated (Box 23, Folder 1545)
  - Piggot, Stuart
    - "David Jones and the Past of Man"
      - Printed version, undated (Box 23, Folder 1546)
      - Galley, undated (Box 23, Folder 1547)
  - Ping-hsin (Bing Xin)
    - "From: 'A Maze of Stars,'" translated by John Cayley, typescript, undated (Box 23, Folder 1548)
  - Pinsky, Robert
    - "from 'An Explanation of America'"
      - Typescript, undated (Box 23, Folder 1549)
      - Galleys, with author's corrections, undated (Box 23, Folder 1550)
    - "Hardy, Ransom, Berryman: A 'Curious Air'"
      - Typescript, corrected, undated (Box 23, Folder 1551)
      - Galley, with author's corrections, undated (Box 23, Folder 1551a)
    - Untitled article: typescript, 1972 (Box 23, Folder 1552)
      With: TLS to Donald Davie from Robert Pinsky, 1972 Feb 1
  - Poole, Robert
    - "The Poetry of C. H. Sisson"
      - Typescript, undated (Box 23, Folder 1553)
      - Galley, with author's corrections, undated (Box 23, Folder 1554)
      - Galley, corrected, undated (Box 23, Folder 1555)
  - Popescu, Petru
    - "Girls in Passing," typescript, undated (Box 23, Folder 1556)
    - Untitled article, typescript, corrected, undated (Box 23, Folder 1557)
  - Porter, Peter
    - "Versions from Martial," typescript, undated (Box 23, Folder 1558)
  - Porteus, Hugh Gordon
    - [Review] "A Man Apart," galley, with author's corrections, undated (Box 23, Folder 1559)
    - "World's End," typescript, 1952 Nov 11 (Box 23, Folder 1560)
  - Pound, Dorothy
    - Notes, holograph, photocopy, 1970 Mar (Box 23, Folder 1561)
  - Pound, Ezra
    - "Arthur Symons," printed version, undated (Box 23, Folder 1562)
    - "Battle Dawn" and "For Italico," printed version, photocopy, and typed note to [William] Cookson from M[ary de Rachewiltz], n.y. Jul 29, Aug 7 (Box 23, Folder 1563)
    - "Canto 115"
      - Typescript, photocopy, with a note by Desmond O'Grady?, undated (Box 23, Folder 1564)
      - Typescript, corrected, undated (Box 23, Folder 1565)
      - Galley, corrected (Box 23, Folder 1566)
        - With: typed note to [William] Cookson from Mary de Rachewiltz, 1980 Mar 22
    - "Cantos LXXII and LXXIII," translated from the Italian by Richard Reid
      - Typescript, corrected, undated (Box 23, Folder 1567)
      - Galley, corrected, undated (Box 23, Folder 1568)
      - Galley, undated (Box 23, Folder 1569)
    - "Divorce Reform"
      - Typescript, corrected, 1916 Jan 20 (Box 23, Folder 1570)
      - Galley, undated (Box 23, Folder 1571)
    - "Four Steps"
      - Printed version, 1977 (Box 23, Folder 1572)
      - Galley, corrected, 1977 (Box 23, Folder 1573)
    - "Four Uncollected Literary Essays"
      "Lytton Strachey on Leftover Celebrity"
      - Printed version, photocopy, 2c., 1918 Oct (Box 23, Folder 1574)
      - Galley, corrected, undated (Box 23, Folder 1575)
      - Galley, undated (Box 23, Folder 1576)
      - [Review] "Merit", printed version, photocopy, 1933 Jun 23 (Box 23, Folder 1577)
      - [Review] "Purgatory," printed version, photocopy, 1938 Sep (Box 23, Folder 1578)
      - "Shaw and Journalism," typescript, corrected, 1920 Jan 1 (Box 23, Folder 1579)
    - "Slice of Life (Fable)," printed version, photocopy, 1939 Jan (Box 23, Folder 1580)
  - Pound, Omar S.
    - "Poems From the Persian and Arabic 500 - 1400 a.d.," typescript, corrected, undated (Box 23, Folder 1581)
    - Untitled article, galley, corrected, undated (Box 23, Folder 1582)
  - Pritchard, William H.
    - "Hardy's Anonymous Sincerity"
      - Typescript, corrected, undated (Box 24, Folder 1583)
      - Galley, with author's corrections, undated (Box 24, Folder 1584)
  - Prunty, Wyatt
    - "Allegory to Causality: Robert Lowell's Poetic Shift," typescript, undated (Box 24, Folder 1585)
    - "The Green Lake," typescript, undated (Box 24, Folder 1586)
    - "Husband," typescript, undated (Box 24, Folder 1587)
  - Quartermain, Peter A.
    - "Basil Bunting Talks About Briggflatts," typescript, undated (Box 24, Folder 1588)
  - Rachewiltz, Mary de
    - "Fragments of an Atmosphere"
      - Typescript, corrected, undated (Box 24, Folder 1589)
      - Galley, with author's corrections, undated (Box 24, Folder 1590)
      - Galley, undated (Box 24, Folder 1591)
        See also: Thomas Hardy, Box 13 folder 918
  - Raine, Kathleen
    - [Review] "Four Points of a Satire," typescript, corrected, undated (Box 24, Folder 1592)
    - [Review] "Jan Le Witt," typescript, corrected, undated (Box 24, Folder 1593)
    - "A Letter," galley, with author's corrections, undated (Box 24, Folder 1594)
  - Rayne, Eric
    - "Autumn Elegy," typescript, undated (Box 24, Folder 1595)
    - "Reading History," typescript, undated (Box 24, Folder 1596)
    - "Take Two," typescript, undated (Box 24, Folder 1597)
  - Read, Herbert
    - "Two Kinds of Poetry," typescript, corrected, undated (Box 24, Folder 1598)
  - Reck, Michael
    - "As If," typescript, undated (Box 24, Folder 1599)
    - "At a Photograph Exhibition," typescript, undated (Box 24, Folder 1600)
    - "Autumn Song," typescript, undated (Box 24, Folder 1601)
    - "Bolzano," typescript, undated (Box 24, Folder 1602)
    - "Confession," typescript, undated (Box 24, Folder 1603)
    - "Dancer," typescript, undated (Box 24, Folder 1604)
    - "The Dreamer King," typescript, undated (Box 24, Folder 1605)
    - "Encounter," typescript, undated (Box 24, Folder 1606)
    - "Farmyard," typescript, undated (Box 24, Folder 1607)
    - "A few working principles:," typescript, undated (Box 24, Folder 1608)
    - "Fire Swan," typescript, undated (Box 24, Folder 1609)
    - "For Bracque on His Birthday," typescript, undated (Box 24, Folder 1610)
    - "Hora Mortis," typescript, undated (Box 24, Folder 1611)
    - "I Assure You," typescript, undated (Box 24, Folder 1612)
    - "In the Friedhof," typescript, undated (Box 24, Folder 1613)
    - "Katrinka," typescript, undated (Box 24, Folder 1614)
    - "Memory," typescript, undated (Box 24, Folder 1615)
    - "Near Cayey, Puerto Rico," typescript, undated (Box 24, Folder 1616)
    - "News Report," typescript, undated (Box 24, Folder 1617)
    - "Observations," typescript, undated (Box 24, Folder 1618)
    - "Observations 2," typescript, undated (Box 24, Folder 1619)
    - "Poet," typescript, undated (Box 24, Folder 1620)
    - "Waka Expressing Ideals of the Tea Ceremony," typescript, undated (Box 24, Folder 1621)
  - Redgrove, Peter
    - "Very Early Among the Islands"
      - Typescript, undated (Box 24, Folder 1622)
      - Galley, with author's corrections, 1977 Jul 26 (Box 24, Folder 1623)
      - Galley, corrected, undated (Box 24, Folder 1624)
  - Rehder, Robert. M
    - "The Sunbather," typescript, undated (Box 24, Folder 1625)
    - "Thunder Without Sound," typescript, undated (Box 24, Folder 1626)
    - "Two Poems"
      - Typescript, undated (Box 24, Folder 1627)
      - Galley, with author's corrections, undated (Box 24, Folder 1628)
    - "Van Gogh: Auvers," typescript, undated (Box 24, Folder 1629)
    - Untitled poem, typescript, undated (Box 24, Folder 1630)
  - Rehder, Robert M., (translator)
    - "Hai," and untitled poem from "Hafiz," typescript, undated (Box 24, Folder 1631)
  - Reid, Denis
    - "Morning," typescript, undated (Box 24, Folder 1632)
  - Reid, Richard
    - "Ezra Pound Asking"
      - Typescript, corrected, undated (Box 24, Folder 1633)
      - Galley, corrected, undated (Box 24, Folder 1634)
      - Galley, corrected, undated (Box 24, Folder 1635)
  - Reverdy, Pierre
    - "Another Explanation of the Mystery," translated by Anthony Rudolf, typescript, undated (Box 24, Folder 1636)
    - "The Blood of the Souls," translated by Anthony Rudolf, typescript, undated (Box 24, Folder 1637)
    - "Changing Looks," translated by Anthony Rudolf, typescript, undated (Box 24, Folder 1638)
    - "Descent," translated by Anthony Rudolf, typescript, undated (Box 24, Folder 1639)
    - "Five Poems from Roof Slates (1918)," translated by Keith Bosley
      - Typescript, corrected, undated (Box 24, Folder 1640)
      - Galley, corrected, undated (Box 24, Folder 1641)
    - "Space," translated by Anthony Rudolf, typescript, undated (Box 24, Folder 1642)
    - "Story," translated by Anthony Rudolf, typescript, undated (Box 24, Folder 1643)
    - "Wing Flap," translated by Anthony Rudolf, typescript, undated (Box 24, Folder 1644)
    - Untitled poem, translated by Anthony Rudolf, typescript, undated (Box 24, Folder 1645)
  - Richards, I. A.
    - "A Talk on 'The Childermass'," typescript, corrected, incomplete draft, 1951 Nov 4 (Box 24, Folder 1646)
  - Rickel, Boyer
    - "Ancil's Lament"
      - Typescript, undated (Box 24, Folder 1647)
      - Galley, with author's corrections, 1977 Feb 8 (Box 24, Folder 1648)
    - "Arrival," typescript, undated (Box 24, Folder 1649)
  - Rilke, Rainer Maria
    - "Fictitious Biography," typescript, undated (Box 24, Folder 1650)
    - "The Magician," typescript, corrected, undated (Box 24, Folder 1651)
  - Rimbaud, Arthur
    - "Dawn," translated by Caroline Wright, typescript, corrected, undated (Box 24, Folder 1652)
  - Robbins, Ruth
    - "The Word Notes of C. M. Doughty"
      - Galley, with author's corrections, undated (Box 24, Folder 1653)
      - Galley, corrected, undated (Box 24, Folder 1654)
  - Robertson, Alasdair
    - "At Samyé ling," typescript, undated (Box 24, Folder 1655)
  - Robertson, Robin
    - "Brattach Sidh," typescript, undated (Box 24, Folder 1656)
    - "Two Poems"
      - Typescript, undated (Box 24, Folder 1657)
      - Galley, with author's correction and typescript, 1979 Jul 23 (Box 24, Folder 1658)
  - Rokeah, David
    - "Decipher," translated by Ruth and Matthew Mead in collaboration with David Rokeah, typescript, undated (Box 24, Folder 1659)
    - "Ijara," translated by Ruth and Matthew Mead in collaboration with David Rokeah
      - Typescript, undated (Box 24, Folder 1660)
      - Galley, corrected, undated (Box 24, Folder 1661)
    - "Mosaic," typescript, undated (Box 24, Folder 1662)
    - "No Darkness," translated by Daniela Grunfeld and Colin Falck, typescript, undated (Box 24, Folder 1663)
    - "Poems," translated by Bernard Lewis, typescript, undated (Box 24, Folder 1664)
    - "Two Poems," translated by Ruth and Matthew Mead, typescript, undated (Box 24, Folder 1665)
  - Rosenthal, M. L.
    - "As For Love," typescript, undated (Box 24, Folder 1666)
    - "One Afternoon," typescript, undated (Box 24, Folder 1667)
    - "Our Neurotic Angel: Robert Lowell (1917-1977)," typescript, corrected, undated (Box 24, Folder 1668)
    - "Three Poems," typescript and printed version, undated (Box 24, Folder 1669)
  - Rossetti, Dante Gabriel
    - Untitled poem, typescript, photocopy, with annotations in an unidentified hand, undated (Box 25, Folder 1670)
      With: 4 translations by Anthony Bonner, Norman Cameron, John Payne, and Ezra Pound, typescript, photocopy, undated
  - Russell, Peter
    - "Breaking Up?," typescript, corrected, 1969 Mar 14 (Box 25, Folder 1671)
    - "The Contemporary Poet's Creative Process, typescript, undated (Box 25, Folder 1672)
    - "Eight Poems," typescript, 1970-83 (Box 25, Folder 1673)
    - "1st April 1984 (Sonnet No. 452)," typescript, 1984 Apr 1 (Box 25, Folder 1674)
    - "Heiligensee," typescript, 1964 Feb 27 (Box 25, Folder 1675)
    - "Manuela's Poems," typescript, 1969 (Box 25, Folder 1676)
    - "Paysages Légendaires," typescript, 1968 (Box 25, Folder 1677)
    - "Winged Amor Painted Blind," typescript, 1964 Mar (Box 25, Folder 1678)
    - Untitled collection of poems, typescript, 1962-63 (Box 25, Folder 1679)
  - Sandars, Nancy K.
    - [Review] "Beowulf," typescript, corrected, undated (Box 25, Folder 1680)
    - "From The Epic of Baal "
      - Typescript, corrected, undated (Box 25, Folder 1681)
      - Galley, with author's corrections, undated
      - Galley, corrected, undated (Box 25, Folder 1682)
    - "In the Margins of Paradise," typescript, corrected, undated (Box 25, Folder 1683)
    - "The Irrelevance of Incest to Oedipus," typescript, corrected, undated (Box 25, Folder 1684)
    - "A Prehistorian's Look at the Literary Uses and Abuses of Myth and Ritual"
      - Typescript, corrected, undated (Box 25, Folder 1685)
      - Galleys, with author's corrections, 3c., undated (Box 25, Folder 1686)
    - "Some thoughts arising from David Jones's latest published writings"
      - Typescript, corrected, undated (Box 25, Folder 1687)
      - Galley, corrected, undated (Box 25, Folder 1688)
    - "Three Part Soliloquy," typescript, undated (Box 25, Folder 1689)
  - Sandy, Stephen
    - "Spider," printed version, undated (Box 25, Folder 1690)
  - Sappho [translated by Peter Whigham]
    - "Agallide," typescript, undated (Box 25, Folder 1691)
    - "The Alibi," typescript, undated (Box 25, Folder 1692)
    - "The Apple," typescript, undated (Box 25, Folder 1693)
    - "The Bridegroom," typescript, undated (Box 25, Folder 1694)
    - "The Girl," typescript, undated (Box 25, Folder 1695)
    - "Her Gifts," typescript, undated (Box 25, Folder 1696)
    - "The Nightingale," typescript, corrected, undated (Box 25, Folder 1697)